He is back and blocking right away.
Pam Forrest,
Saquon Barkley who is trying to get
going after Rocky's start to the season.
There is the push.
Let's see where they spot this ball.
Officials were lined up at the 46 running straight up.
It's baked into everything they do
and everything they are as an offense.
Sticking with it on the ground.
This is Tank Bigsby,
the former Jacksonville Jaguars.
Again here on third down.
Look at all the shifting by the Minnesota
defense.
Barkley is going to run it on third and long.
They'll get inside the 40. That ball is loose,
but they're going to be
whistled down by contact.
Eight back in coverage this time for Minnesota.
Hertz pointing, throwing,
trying to find a loose man.
It's A.J.
Brown.
He's in.
Touchdown Eagles on the opening drive.
This Eagles offense getting back to who they've been.
This drive embodies it about as well
as you can imagine.
Metellus,
he's kind of a hybrid safety linebacker.
That is not a
great matchup on A.J.
Brown.
Two of the best wide receivers in the game.
Wentz fires to the third wide receiver.
Minnesota,
day,
Nevada feeling back with the Vikings
this year picks up 10. 31% of their third
downs.
That's 9% below league average and
it's one of the worst marks in the NFL.
So they convert to stay on the field and
Wentz takes a shot for Jordan Addison.
It is going to be ruled a catch down inside.
The top pass catcher of the other side of the ball.
You had Jefferson on the near side that time.
Off that run play.
Right read, wrong throw.
Oh, bad snap.
Over the head of Rex. That's a live ball
and Wentz will rescue it back there.
It was being chased down by Aziz Ojalary.
Just did two snaps and now Will Reichard who's hit a 62
yarder this year already.
Will bury it from 59. Four man rush hurts.
Lofts it up there
and it was nearly hauled in by Smith.
He could not hold on and it's the former Philadelphia
Eagle Isaiah Rogers.
He's matured.
He's moved past it.
He's already played Philadelphia
one time with Washington.
First target, Justin Jefferson.
That's a good guy to get some rhythm
for.
Pass the 30 yard line out to the 34 from Minnesota.
It's 18 yards for number 18. Ocean
Addison.
Blitz coming.
Wentz hit as he throws.
Picked off.
Intercepted.
There goes Jaylakes
Hunt.
House call Philadelphia.
His first NFL pick leads to his first touchdown.
What a
great design.
You see they got six up front.
They bring Zach
Vaughn and they just drop right underneath that inside slant.
And with the guy in his face,
Carson Wentz just doesn't see
him unless they turn this around drastically in the next two
downs.
Wentz is rolling out.
Looking down field.
Launches a
ball.
Dangerous pass.
Intercepted.
Picked off by Andrew
Mokuba who's the only defensive back for Philadelphia that has a
pick.
Hurts.
Swings it out.
And not a whole lot of room for
Shipley.
Isaiah Rogers is there for the stops.
He hasn't really
had a chance to practice much in the last month plus.
Carson
Wentz gets his fourth straight start today.
It's been a rocky
last handful of plays.
Let's see if that gets them back on track.
Speedy Nailer on a floating.
Wentz passed down the sideline.
The run game just isn't real explosive.
Wentz slings it for Jefferson off the back foot.
In space.
Let him make the play.
Justin Jefferson still going down inside the 20.
Just make good decisions at quarterback and the plays can be there.
Off the fake.
Wentz outside.
Here's Oliver.
And Mokuba is there to bring him down.
Fake it to Mason.
Flag is thrown.
Ball is thrown.
It is a touchdown for Nailer.
We'll check the penalty flag though.
This is coming back for a hold.
Yeah, Brando.
So from 34,
just about the length of an extra point.
He's the play caller, the
green dot.
And he's coming in on a blitz.
Hurts flips it.
Got her.
And he'll get tackled
as the Vikings rally to the ball and force a third consecutive
stop.
Extra body coming for Philadelphia.
Wentz slings
Jefferson first down.
He steps out of bounds.
Clock will keep
moving up until the two minute warning but.
Hockinson in
motion.
Wentz pumps holding on to the ball for a really long
time.
Still pumping.
Trying to maneuver.
Stops.
Throws.
Nobody
there.
Being indoors helps that distance as well.
So Hurts
underneath.
They get a completion.
And they have not
been able to get much traction.
Remember, they have a defensive
touchdown today.
Hurts come back route.
And Devontae Smith.
Right
back to work near the 40. Byron Murphy is there for the stop.
34 seconds left.
You gotta be careful next time they don't double move them
and run right by them when you sit flat footed like that.
Here is a blitz.
An extra body for Minnesota.
Hurts trying to avoid it.
He will not.
They catch up to him.
Philadelphia may have to use another timeout.
This to be a group thing.
Complementary football.
Good stuff,
Pam. Here is Mason against this Philadelphia defense.
Challenge this middle and deep zone with this Eagles defense.
Toss play.
Mason finds a seam.
Takes it down inside the 35 yard lines.
Philadelphia is kind of cindered in some makeup and prosthetics.
Darius Frost the alter ego now.
Here is Mason.
Another big run along the edges.
This has been a problem for Philadelphia's defense.
Philadelphia is going to play coverage here.
Underneath Hawkinson.
Bohn is there along with Dijin.
Minnesota had only failed to score a touchdown
in the red zone five times on 15 trips.
They have failed three times today.
It is Brett Toth at center.
With Juergens dealing with an injury.
Deep drop for Hurts.
Trying to find something down field.
And it is Devontae Smith.
He is loose.
He has got it.
He is gone.
Touchdown Eagles.
Lightning strike to Devontae Smith.
There you go.
We talk about being aggressive under center.
Play action.
And just the double move and the speed
on the outside by Devontae Smith.
Toth against Isaiah Rogers the former eagle.
That is an element of this offense that I think
they can continue to expand in a more
traditional four down nickel defense.
That means Dijin is the slot corner.
There is Hawkinson over the middle.
Fires to Naylor.
And incomplete.
He drove that ball on that speed out.
It is a big time throw.
To get the 11 yards.
Now it is Hawkinson over the middle in front of Bohn.
There is the first down again.
This feels like a critical moment
in the game here in the second half.
So Wedge steps up and delivers to the sideline to Jordan Addison.
And a first down.
He has got to come set.
He does.
Wildcat snap.
It is Mason to the left.
He looked to be short.
Zach Bohn running laterally with the back Mason.
Another good stop for Philly.
Trying to play off
the Detroit Lions game from the other night against Kansas City.
Take a look.
It is really close.
All you young running backs at home.
He broke the plane.
Less than 100
seconds for the third.
Here is Hertz stepping up.
Flag is thrown far side.
Hertz throws near
side for Devontae Smith.
It will be good for a first down pending the flag.
75 seconds for
the third up by five.
Deep drop.
Looking for something down field.
Hertz for Smith.
He
holds on despite the Smith hit.
There is a flag thrown as well.
The little field will
run it.
And Barkley doesn't have anything there.
He runs right into Jalen Redmond.
He is lucky
he didn't get called for being offside.
Elliott.
No good.
Wide to the right.
His first field
goal miss of the season.
Deep drop for Wentz,
Fires it.
got Addison in stride inside the 40 of Philadelphia.
Another deep drop.
Wentz pumps and throws out route that has
been killing the Philly defense today and
it has been a staple.
They got all three corners on the same side of the field.
Wentz looks in that direction,
he ends up taking the sack and it's Moro O'Jomo.
This man coverage,
you'll see they got no corners here on the back side.
Zach Vaughn.
Wentz stepping up,
maneuvers around the defender and
picks up a first down with his legs.
O'Jomo comes away with a big sack.
So Rikert again from 35,
his fourth make of the day.
He's still in the game though,
there he is right there in the slot.
Can't miss him with
those bright green shoes.
Hertz collapsing pocket,
got away from Turner,
being chased
by Turner, throws on the move, it is AJ Brown.
Hertz looks,
throws open man,
Devontae Smith,
nobody was near him when he
caught it.
Five on the pressure,
Hertz throws down the scene,
AJ
Brown touchdown,
his second of the day.
Keeping his eyes down
on the field, a simple double post.
Devontae Smith holds the safety,
AJ Brown's the outside
post and Jordan Addison with a hundred yard receiving game today.
Has been Wentz's favorite
target so far in this last month and sure
enough on cue he steps out near midfield,
it's a first down.
Three points,
points in general are necessary right now.
Wentz still
can't step up into a throw,
he's going to take off again and he's going to pick up another
first down with his legs.
They're going to run it two yards for
the game and they're going to get it to Addison and he's out of
bounds inside of three minutes.
Oh, a roll of the dice.
It's not there,
just throw it through the upright,
stop the
clock and play second down.
Instead it's second and 18,
they go right back to Hockinson,
back down near the 12,
clock continues to move either way.
So right,
Gerd slides that one through inside the right upright.
Up here with Isaiah Rogers,
one on one against AJ Brown.
It is Hertz launching it,
AJ Brown is loose and AJ Brown has it.
And that might have sealed the game for
Philadelphia on a huge third down conversion.
Lead the rest of the clock,
they still have a remaining timeout.
They can get every second out of this.
He's going to stay tall, stay tall.
And they still haven't gotten him down.
Forward progress now gets whistled,
now the clock's inside of 40,
it's about right there.
There it is, down to two seconds.
That is the key number of this ball game today.
Still third down.
Yeah, that.
Welcome those of you who've watched other games across the country,
we're getting you set for commanders,
cowboys,
some of you will see Packers,
Cardinals.